如果你的应用程序
If you run it on your phone, your App crashed
因为NetworkOnMainException而崩溃了
because of a network got main thread exception. We found
我们可以将设备和电脑连接
this answer by connecting our device to our computer and
然后观察Android设备监视器上显示的错误信息
then checking Android device monitor for the error. You can
可以看到这里是我们的应用程序包名
see here that this is our package name and this
这里是进程ID 如果你搜索这个进程ID
is our process ID. If you search the logs for
就会看到错误信息 这个错误是被NetworkOnMainThreadException引发的
that process ID then our error appears. It's triggered ultimately
也就是在主线程中进行了网络操作
by a network on main thread exception. If you're curious
如果你想知道是我们代码中的哪一行触发的
as to what line of our code actually caused
你可以向下滚动这个堆栈信息
this, you can scroll down the stack trace to
这些是系统库中代码引发的错误信息 你可以跳过
read more. This is our framework code that you
而这里是我们代码中触发错误的元凶
can skip and here's where it actually hits our
这行包含了错误发生的地点 在PlaceholderFragment.class中的onCreateView()方法中
app. It's within the placeholder fragment class, in the onCreateView method. And
具体是在MainActivity.java的116行
it happens in main activity.java file, in line 116. So
回到代码 在这一行你可以看到urlConnection.connect()
if we go back to the code, on that line you can see that urlConnection.connect
实际上就是它引发了错误 我们不能在主线程里使用它
actually caused the error, and that we can't do that on the main thread.